Contact

aaronper@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aaronperezrn (LinkedIn) www.ajiana.com (Personal) www.memorialhermann.org (Company)

Top Skills
PALS
ACLS
Acute Care

Aaron Perez

Emergency Room Nurse

Kailua, Hawaii

Summary

I have been a Registered Nurse since 1999 and have worked in many areas across the medical spectrum. I have worked in surgical units, IMU, Orthopedics, Special Diseases, Oncology and Emergency Room Departments in the acute care setting. I spent a year in the long-term setting as a Nursing supervisor and ADON early in my career before transitioning back into the acute care setting. The bulk of my nursing experience is in ER and Trauma services, an area I have found to constantly capture my interest. Concurrent to my nursing career I have also assisted and or developed several small businesses including a cell phone store, a dish network franchise and an exotic car rental website. I am currently working on a national restaurant guide. I enjoy challenges and look forward to learning opportunities.

Specialties: Emergency room services. CEN, PALS, ACLS, TNCC, ONC, NIHSS, ABLS. I function as a preceptor and throughout my career have functioned in a charge capacity.

Experience

Castle Medical Center Emergency Room RN September 2015 - Present (4 years 11 months) Kailua, Hawaii

Charge nurse.

Ajiana inc CEO January 2015 - Present (5 years 7 months)

Memorial Hermann Healthcare System Emergency Room RN 4 November 2005 - Present (14 years 9 months) Function as an RN in the emergency room.

Precept new employees and assist with staff development.

Assume charge nurse roles and duties.

Created and manage two committees for education and employee retention.

Assist with process improvement and creation of policy and procedure for the ER.

2005-2009 RN at Memorial Hermann Premier

Worked for systems office filling needs at nine of the Memorial Hermann ER's.

Functioned in many roles from RN to charge nurse.

Twelve Oaks Medical Center

RN

January 2001 - January 2005 (4 years 1 month)

Mariner Health Woodwind Lakes

Nursing Supervisor and interim ADON

June 2000 - November 2001 (1 year 6 months)

Park Plaza Hospital

RN

May 1999 - July 2000 (1 year 3 months)

Education

University of Texas

BSN; 2012, BSN · (2010 - 2012)

Houston Community College

ADON, Applied Sciences · (1996 - 1999)